CONTACT



+91 98798 81409



mitul.chhabhaya90@gmail.com



mitul90.github.io/porfolio.github.io



linkedin.com/in/mitul-chhabhaya

LANGUAGES

98%
95%
100%
75%
75%
95%
90%
80%
95%

SKILLS

Design	to	HT	ML

	100%
WordPress Front-end	
	95%
ACF (Advance Custom Field)	
	95%
Shopify Front-end	
	95%
GIT	
	80%

MITUL CHHABHAYA

Front-end Developer

About



I am a front-end web developer with 10+ years of experience has developed 100+ websites and helped multiple clients. Specialize in high-quality HTML, SCSS, CSS, JavaScript, NextJs, ReactJs, ReactBootstrap, and JQuery. Customizing WordPress, and Shopify themes, and experience in Chrome extension development.

Happy to help you build websites with optimized page speed and SEO-friendly.

Experience



SEP 2023 - PRESENT Beardog Digital Sr. Front-end Developer

JAN 2020 - SEP 2023 NAVINES Sr. Front-end Developer

APR 2019 - DEC 2019 Spinx Digital Sr. Front-end Developer

AUG 2016 - APR 2019 Shreeji Web Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Sr. Front-end Developer

SEP 2013 - AUG 2016 Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd. TL / Sr. Web Designer

FEB 2013 - SEP 2013 Global Easy web Solution Web Designer

Education



APRIL 2014 Saurashtra University M.Com KK Parekh Commerce College – Amreli

Achievement



APR 2015 Certificate Of Appreciation Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

AUG 2014 Excellent Performer Of The Month Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

NOV 2013 Rising Star Of The Month Nichetech Computer Solutions Pvt. Ltd

Certification



NOV 2012 Certificate In Web Design Red & White Multimedia Education - Surat